hey everybody this is jeff from canal
sound light and we're coming back to you
with another video and this time we're
going over the adj
focus spot 6z
[Music]
so we're excited to show you the adj
focusbot 6e
it has a 300 watt cool white led engine
as you can see boom now let's go through
the colors
has two color wheels two global wheels
two prism wheels motorized focus
motorized zoom motorized iris
and two frost filters as well as all of
that
so let's go through the colors color
wheel number one has a
mainly primary colors as you can see
it's pretty cool
color wheel number two has a bunch of
different colors and it also has cto
ctb and a fluorescent blue or uv
let's dig in deeper into that we have
the cto
which is stands for color temperature
orange
which actually produces like a bit of a
warm white right here as you can see
we have ctb which is stands for color
temperature blue
and it's a bit of a cooler white as you
can see
if you pair this up with the the frost
filter you can watch the whole stage
these different color temperatures
we have the uv right here is pretty cool
actually is we we had this expanded out
like
wide before and we'll show you that it's
amazing
next we'll go through the gobo wheels
these gopro wheels
are pretty cool it has seven gobos adj
chose some really nice gobos for aerial
effects and for projections
or for room uh you know pattern breakups
as you can see that's the other gobo
wheel right here
it's got one glass gobo it's about to
show up right there
that's a rainbow glass gobo and next up
we have the prisms
this is the circular prism the six-facet
circular prism
we have the six-faceted linear prism and
we'll show you what what the gobos
looks like in those prisms so right now
you have that
circular prism with the gobo in there it
shows you how
how nice that looks
shows you the gobo rotation right here
and we have the linear prism that looks
like that
pretty cool right the cool thing about
this fixture
is that it has also an iris
as you can see we have the motorized
iris kind of going flickering in and out
in and out in and out
but you can also do different things you
can make a narrow focus
all the way into a particular subject
that you want to focus in on
this is what i mean by a narrow focus on
the iris so you can
close that in and pinpoint that focus on
a specific subject you can also
you know zoom out a little bit or or
what do you call it unfocus that a
little bit so you can
not have that straight hard edge next
feature that we want to show you it's a
zoom range which has a pretty wide
zoom range going from a 9 degree
all the way up to 28
so pretty wide zoom range and you can
layer this on the
on the frosts filters and and the gobos
and you could do a lot with that
you know you can play a lot with that
like i mentioned it has
two uh washes so one is a light wash
which is what you can see here
which means like it's a smaller range
wash and then we can
we can show you the difference by going
to the wide wash which is
bam see that see how wide of a coverage
that is
it's pretty amazing you can layer on top
of this
another prism to even do a little bit
wider if you wanted to
next up here we wanted to show you the
global morphing so it has two gobo
wheels that you can kind of
play play off of each other so
chicken over here programmed a couple of
global morphing
scenes for you to see chicken is our
lighting
programmer over here and he's behind the
camera
so check this out we have another gobo
wheeler
global morphing thing right here it's
pretty cool
we have another little cross overlaid
with the other gobo
this is a pretty cool one right here
these are just different ideas for
global morphing there's plenty of things
that you can do with that
we just didn't want to do some of the
other ones that you've seen already
so this is a nice little flower
multi-color flower effect
you can mix the gobo morphing with the
gobo shake to give you a nice
dynamic effect that you see here you can
add some colors
you know you could do you can add the
iris back into it
so just sky's the limit with this a lot
of different combinations that are
available
my my favorite thing about it is the
prisms
as you can see especially with that lime
color on the on the color wheel
each color wheel by the way has six
colors plus um
plus open or white and so
i really like this circular
prism with the spiral
gobo let's go over some more features
back to the cto as you can see we've
laid
we layered on a wash on top of it
so this is like a nice perfect scene for
any kind of performance
or ctb or that uv
that we talked about so to summarize
this is a pro light
by adj it's got a nice big fan to keep
everything very cool
it's got a locking mechanism on the pan
and tilt
arms it's got trucon in and out
along with network capability for artnet
it's got three pin and five pin uh
dmx it's got a nice little screen over
here with a firmware
uh port usb for upgrading
perfect for any production company any
install
nightclub mainly like a good
a good option for a theater or a church
this is a beautiful light we hope you
enjoyed watching this video
please like and subscribe this video big
announcement
we have merch coming out so uh be on the
lookout for that
like i said check out our other social
media pages on instagram
and we'll see you in the next video